[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal was the number one predator of the Moa?", "correct_answer": "An extinct species of eagle", "incorrect_answers": ["They had no predator they were too large", "An extinct species of lion", "An extinct species of wolf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the movie Ghost premiere?", "correct_answer": "1990", "incorrect_answers": ["1991", "1989", "1992"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movies has monster producer Jerry Bruckheimer worked on, apart from the 2009 3-D action comedy G-Force?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Armageddon", "Pirates of the Caribbean", "Pearl Harbor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Leonardo da Vincis art teacher?", "correct_answer": "Andrea del Verrocchio", "incorrect_answers": ["Fra Luca Paccioli", "Titian", "Giotto di Bondone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If an object scatters light in all wavelengths, what color does it appear to be?", "correct_answer": "White", "incorrect_answers": ["Transparent", "Black", "Invisible"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the first book by Darwin that directly dealt with evolution?", "correct_answer": "On the Origins of the Species", "incorrect_answers": ["Essay on the Principles of Population", "Totem and Taboo", "The Descent of Man and the Selection in Relation to Sex"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the U.S. state of Utah mean in the Ute language?", "correct_answer": "People of the mountains", "incorrect_answers": ["Spirits of the rivers", "Children of the winds", "Land around the great lake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Blazing Saddles, before becoming the first black sheriff in town, Bart met a drunk in the cells that became his ally. What name was this man better known by?", "correct_answer": "The Waco Kid", "incorrect_answers": ["Quick Draw McGraw", "Dead Eye Dick", "Mongo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does for rock and roll what The Sound of Music did for hills is the tag line from which movie?", "correct_answer": "This Is Spinal Tap", "incorrect_answers": ["The School Of Rock", "24hr Party People", "Almost Famous"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 2001 maniacs, the teens take a detour that leads them to the town of Pleasant Valley, Georgia and are invited to stay for the towns celebration. What is the name of the celebration?", "correct_answer": "Guts and Glory Jubilee", "incorrect_answers": ["Independence Celebration", "The South Will Rise Again", "Confederate Remembrance Day"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of these actors did not star in Tootsie.", "correct_answer": "Larry Gelbart", "incorrect_answers": ["Jessica Lange", "Teri Garr", "Dustin Hoffman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following quote is from which hit movie?  \nYou can be too old for a lot of things, but youre never too old to be afraid.", "correct_answer": "Home Alone", "incorrect_answers": ["Memento", "The Little Rascals", "Fat Albert"]}]